<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>19hours</title>
    <link>https://19hours.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 19hours</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://19hours.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hire me</title>
      <link>https://19hours.net/hire/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://19hours.net/hire/</guid>
      <description>I offer software development services and I am based in Singapore. I am available for hire on contract basis. My expertise are listed below.
MVP and SaaS development  Have an idea? I can develop your MVP or SaaS so you can focus on the business side of things. Leave the technical side of things to me  Website and application scraping  Web and data scraping to automate your job Run scripts to scrape data from websites without public APIs  Scripting  Speed up your work flow by removing manual and time-consuming tasks Run scripts to connect to various APIs and send SMS or notifications when something happens  Web design (HTML5/CSS3)  Integrate your brand colors into a coherent web design Custom pages, landing pages, dashboards Interactive and modern design  Web development  Web applications with logic to do various things Connect to third-party APIs like LinkedIn Plugin development for Wordpress and Shopify  Cross-platform development  Develop iOS, Android, Linux, Mac, Windows and CLI applications  Reverse engineering  Help you to find and document hidden APIs behind applications Decompile mobile applications to find bugs and loopholes (Authorisation required from app developer)  Rate US$90/hour</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buttery smooth home network</title>
      <link>https://19hours.net/posts/buttery-smooth-home-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://19hours.net/posts/buttery-smooth-home-network/</guid>
      <description>Working at home is nice and comfy but a flaky internet connection can make everyone go crazy. So this morning I took the spare routers that you get from recontracting your ISP plans to reproduce a 4g internet experience at home. It&amp;rsquo;s super fast and convenient because every device switches to the best access point on its own. No more manually switching to different bands when you&amp;rsquo;re close to the router and when you&amp;rsquo;re not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tracking Singapore law with git</title>
      <link>https://19hours.net/posts/tracking-singapore-law-with-git/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://19hours.net/posts/tracking-singapore-law-with-git/</guid>
      <description>Because the elections are coming, I tried to understand what laws were introduced and what changes were made to the laws since the last election. I visited sso.agc.gov.sg and they have this timeline box on each page and you have to select a date to see a version of the statute. There was no way to compare different versions on the same screen.
Today, I created a git repository to track all changes to the statutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Supermarket wars</title>
      <link>https://19hours.net/posts/supermarket-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://19hours.net/posts/supermarket-wars/</guid>
      <description>When I was younger, one of the most frustrating things I had to do was to book a badminton court. You had to be ready two weeks before the actual day to spam the refresh key until the portal released the bookings. I was always so annoyed because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t figure out how it was possible for people in their 50s to be clicking faster than me. Back then, simply using a fast computer and having multiple tabs would beat most people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trace Together&#39;s privacy, or lack thereof</title>
      <link>https://19hours.net/posts/trace-togethers-privacy-or-lack-thereof/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://19hours.net/posts/trace-togethers-privacy-or-lack-thereof/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days ago, I saw the announcement for a new app called TraceTogether. It’s an app by the government to make contact tracing easier. The app appeared on a lot of news websites because it’s a good smart nation initiative.
I was interested to find out how Bluetooth was used. I launched my terminal and decompiled the app using Jadx to find out what’s powering the app.
The app uses bluetooth to log other people’s devices around you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
